Alright we're talking about medium stiffness boots.
Medium stiffness boots are in the range of four to seven pretty much.
Boot manufacturers have a rating scale usually one to ten but a lot of them have different ways to rate how soft their boots are.
Mid boots are probably best if you are just starting I'd say because they're in between soft and hard.
But once again I'd say go to your shop, try them on, ask them how long it takes to break in for that boot manufacturer, they'll let you know.
Try them on, make sure they're comfortable.
Ask them how long they take before they really start breaking down, cause if you ride a lot boots go pretty quickly.
Ask them if they're a warm boot or not because your feet will get cold.
And you should find out because you might want to return your boots if they do not keep your feet warm.
There's many different other things, but I'm discovering the main, what type of boot your looking for, for what type of riding that you want to do.